http://www.sharpesoft.com/about/privacy/

ABOUT SHARPESOFT
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes SharpeSoft’s policies and procedures relating to the collection, use, and disclosure of Your information. SharpeSoft may use Your Personal data to provide and improve its Services. By using a SharpeSoft Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Effective May 5, 2020.
1.Definitions
The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.
For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:
SharpeSoft refers to SharpeSoft, Inc., headquartered in Yuba City, California.
Country refers to the United States.
You or User means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.
Account means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of SharpeSoft’s Service.
Website refers to any content accessible from SharpeSoft.com, SharpeSoft.app, or any other referring URL under SharpeSoft authority.
Application refers to any software program provided by and licensed by SharpeSoft.
Service refers to the applicable SharpeSoft Website, Application, or other content delivered through a third-party Service Provider or Social Media Service.
Service Provider means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of SharpeSoft. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by SharpeSoft to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of SharpeSoft, to perform services related to the Service, or to assist SharpeSoft in analyzing how the Service is used.
Social Media Service refers to any website or any social network website through which a User can log in or create an account to use the Service.
Device means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a mobile phone, or a digital tablet.
Cookies are small files that are placed on Your computer, mobile device, or any other device by a website, containing the details of Your browsing history on that website.
Personal Data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.
Usage Data refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
2. Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using the SharpeSoft Service, you may be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify You. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
Name
Email address
Phone number
Address, City, State/Province, and/or ZIP/Postal code
Usage Data
Usage Data is collected automatically when using the Service and may include information such as Your Device's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), operating system, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser version, the Website pages that You visit, the time and date of Your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other diagnostic data. Information that Your browser sends when You use the Service may also be collected.
3. Tracking Technologies
SharpeSoft uses Cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on the Service and store certain information. Tracking technologies used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze the Service.
You can instruct Your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. However, if You do not accept Cookies, You may not be able to use some parts of the Service.
SharpeSoft may use both session Cookies and persistent Cookies (remain on your device after the current session) for the purposes set out below.
Necessary / Essential Cookies
These session Cookies are essential to provide You with services available through the Website and to enable You to use some of its features. They help to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts and are only used to provide you with those services. Without these Cookies, the services that You have asked for cannot be provided.
Cookies Policy / Notice Acceptance Cookies
These persistent Cookies identify if users have accepted the use of cookies on the Website.
Functionality Cookies
These persistent Cookies allow the Website to remember choices You make when You use the Website, such as remembering your login details or language preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You with a more personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter your preferences every time You use the Website.
Tracking and Performance Cookies
These persistent Cookies are used to track information about traffic to the Website and how users use the Website. The information gathered via these Cookies may directly or indirectly identify you as an individual visitor. This is because the information collected is typically linked to a pseudonymous identifier associated with the device you use to access the Website. SharpeSoft may also use these Cookies to test new advertisements, pages, features, or new functionality of the Website to see how users react to them.
4. Your Data
Use of Your Data
SharpeSoft may use Your data for the following purposes:
To provide and maintain the Service, including to monitor the usage of the Service.
To manage Your registration as a user of the Service. The Personal Data You provide can give You access to different functionalities of the Service that are available to You as a registered user.
To manage Your requests to SharpeSoft, such as support issues, new feature, community interactions, and/or knowledge base articles.
To contact You by email, telephone calls, SMS, or other equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile application's push notifications regarding updates or informative communications related to the functionalities, products or contracted services, including the security updates, when necessary or reasonable for their implementation.
To provide You with news, special offers, and/or general information about additional SharpeSoft products, services, and events.
SharpeSoft may share your personal information in the following situations:
When You share personal information or otherwise interact in the public areas with other users, such information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside. If You interact with other users or register through a Third-Party Social Media Service, Your contacts on the Third-Party Social Media Service may see Your name, profile, pictures, and descriptions of Your activity. Similarly, other users may be able to view descriptions of Your activity, communicate with You, and view Your profile.
With Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of the Service, or to remarket on third-party websites to You after You visited the Service.
With affiliates, in which case SharpeSoft will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include SharpeSoft subsidiaries, subcontractors, joint venture partners, or other companies that SharpeSoft controls or that are under common control.
With business partners to offer You certain products, services, or promotions.
In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of SharpeSoft assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of the SharpeSoft business to another company.
If required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or law enforcement agency).
SharpeSoft may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
Comply with a legal obligation
Protect and defend the rights or property of the Company
Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
Protect the personal safety of Users of the Service or the public
Protect against legal liability
Retention of Your Personal Data
SharpeSoft will retain Your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. SharpeSoft may retain and use Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to resolve disputes, comply with legal obligations, and/or enforce legal agreements and policies.
SharpeSoft will retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of the Service, or SharpeSoft is legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.
Security of Your Personal Data
The security of Your Personal Data is important to SharpeSoft, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While SharpeSoft strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, SharpeSoft cannot guarantee its absolute security.
5. Usage, Performance, and Miscellaneous
SharpeSoft may use third-party Service Providers, such as Google Analytics, to provide better improvement of the Service.
SharpeSoft may use third-party remarketing services to advertise to You on third-party websites.
6. Children's Privacy
SharpeSoft Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. SharpeSoft does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your child has provided SharpeSoft with Personal Data, please contact Us.
7. Links to Other Websites
Our Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. If You click on a third party link, You will be directed to that third party's site. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You visit.
8. Changes to this Privacy Policy
SharpeSoft may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
9. Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact SharpeSoft by email at success@sharpesoft.com.
